### CONTACT



33 1462 5131



bryan 3009@hotmail.com



Guadalajara, Jalisco.



in Bryan Quezada Vásquez

#### LANGUAGES

Spanish

Native

English

Proficient C1

German

Beginner A1

#### TECH SKILLS

MS Excel Visual Basic HTML/CSS C/C++JavaScript Git Python

## SOFT SKILLS

Leadership

SQL

Teamwork

Time Management

Problem-solving

Adaptability

Communication

# **BRYAN ALEJANDRO QUEZADA VASQUEZ**

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER ENGINEER

Workforce administrative with 2+ years of experience skilled in data analysis, planning projections, dashboard development, problem solving (RCA), real time activity and KPI's.

Well-organized with exceptional analytical skills, professional with the ability to manage multiple projects, rises to the challenges under pressure and within deadlines as an exemplary leader.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Workforce Coordinator | Teleperformance 2021 - Present

I supervise the employees within the workforce department, I coordinate with other managers to determine areas that need attention and administer new training plans for the organization.

## Forecast Specialist | Teleperformance

2020 - 2021

I created from scratch to finish forecasting models using data collection, data analysis, and statistical tools. At this point I was able to provide long term staffing projections based on call arrival patterns.

## Mission Control | Teleperformance

2019 - 2020

As a part of a team, I oversaw reporting tasks. Here I designed different types of excel reports and dashboards useful to report KPI's for one of the biggest FinTech companies.

# Supervisor | Teleperformance

2018

I had a 20 people team for one of the biggest banks in US, where my responsibility was to develop high-performance leaders by managing soft skills and providing learning opportunities and taking corrective actions.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Mechatronics Engineering**

2017 - 2021

Centro de enseñanza técnica industrial (CETI Colomos)

#### **Electronics Technologist**

2013 - 2017

Centro de enseñanza técnica industrial (CETI Colomos)

#### COURSES

#### Generation | Java Full-Stack Development

Bootcamp that involves learning Java, HTML5, CSS3, MySQL, to build an entire web app. At the end of this course, it is required to present a web app fully developed with a team we formed.

# Lean Six Sigma | White Belt

2021

First level of certification that provides information about Six Sigma basic concepts.